Hubungi

bagaz.important@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/baghas-rizaluddin-051049243 (LinkedIn)

Keahlian Teratas

Critical Thinking
Easily Adaptable
Promotional Marketing

Languages

Bahasa Indonesia (Native or Bilingual)

Bahasa Inggris (Professional Working)

Certifications

Google Project Management: Specialization

Sertifikat Kelas Mengenal Pemrograman Komputer

Agile Project Management

Baghas Rizaluddin

Team Member of IGV AIESEC in Universitas Brawijaya | Second Year Computer Science Student in Universitas Brawijaya

Jakarta Utara, Jakarta Raya, Indonesia

Ringkasan

Baghas Rizaluddin or usually called Bagas is a minimalism kinda person. He is a planner and problem solver with high integrity and sense of responsibility. He is experienced working in teams, tight deadlines, solving complex problems and more.

Apart from that, he is also interested in existing social problems, economic developments, sports, and technological developments. He is also a person who has firm belief so that he always tries to be a better person than the previous day.

Pengalaman

Society of Renewable Energy Universitas Brawijaya 1 bulan

Staff Accomodation and Technical REVEAL 2024 Februari 2024 - Present (1 bulan)

Member

Februari 2024 - Present (1 bulan)

Society of Renewable Energy Indonesia is a student organization committed to advancing new and renewable energy in Indonesia. Comprises of 40 student chapters established in 40 universities aim to gauge student interest and awareness in renewable energy

AIESEC in Universitas Brawijaya

1 tahun 3 bulan

Team Member | Quality Assurance of On The Map Project, Incoming Global Volunteer Departement September 2023 - Januari 2024 (5 bulan)

- Responsible for finding a Host Family for the exchange participant to stay with for the duration of the project
- Successfully raised 11 host families and 1 boarding house for total 21 exchange participants

- Create a centralized database for host family data and related important data such as MoUs, participant data, adoptive family information and others
- Become a communication mediator between host families and related project parties
- Manage difficulties and solutions for host families during the project

Organizing Committe Member | Delegates Experiences UPSEE Conference 2023

Oktober 2023 - November 2023 (2 bulan)

Organizing Committe On-Site | JOIN AIESEC 2023 Oktober 2023 - Oktober 2023 (1 bulan)

Organizing Committe Member | Customer Experience of Literaction 2.0, Local Project Departement

Februari 2023 - September 2023 (8 bulan)

- Conducted interviews for approximately 90 participants
- Create a registration and payment flow for participants
- Organize and introspect participant registration data
- Carrying out searches and briefs as well as scheduling for approximately 8 speakers for the event
- Creating MoU/LoA for each speaker and participant individually
- Creating interview schedule sheet for registred participants

Organizing Committee Member | Brand and Marketing of Eduphoria, Local Project Departement November 2022 - Februari 2023 (4 bulan)

- Create a marketing strategy for events
- Create promotional media (IG Feed, Story, Poster, etc.) with predetermined times and deadlines
- Manage the course of promotions, during the event registration period
- Make media reports via Social Media, before, during and after the event

Raion Community Internship Trainee Maret 2023 - April 2023 (2 bulan)

In this internship I served as Product Manager and developed an app prototype called StudyHive with a duration of 3 weeks

StudyHive itself is an application that focuses on job training for people with physical disabilities/disabilities and underprivileged children with a collective

registration system, where one person becomes a Facilitator and acts as a person who accommodates participants who wish to register. in courses.

My job is:

- Create wireframes
- Brainstorm app ideas
- · Create a development timeline
- Communicating between programmer division and UI/UX Designer

SMADU CUP

Head Chairman of Competition Oktober 2021 - Agustus 2022 (11 bulan)

On this occasion I served as one of the chief organizers of the competition at the inter-high school competition event, especially in the field of Digital Poster Design.

SMAN 52 Jakarta

Head of Badminton Club SMAN 52 Jakarta Utara Juni 2021 - Februari 2022 (9 bulan)

- Responsible for creating extracurricular development plan
- Responsible to create a fun and comfortable environment to practice
- Responsible making sideplan for the club during pandemic
- Responsible to create digital content for extracurricular activities
- Managing club personal social media

SMADU CUP

Vice Chairman of Competiton November 2019 - Mei 2020 (7 bulan)

- Served as one of the deputy chief executives of inter-high school badminton competitions
- Responsible for setting up the venue and match equipment
- Communicate with the fellow event organizers and participants of the event

Pendidikan

Universitas Brawijaya

Teknik Informatika · (Agustus 2022)

SMAN 52 Jakarta

High School Diploma, Science Major · (2019 - 2022)